<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Magee</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Magee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summarising ESLint issues</title>
      <link>/posts/eslint-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/eslint-summary/</guid>
      <description>npm install eslint-formatter-summary ./node_modules/eslint/bin/eslint.js -f summary ./src </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ox-hugo</title>
      <link>/posts/ox-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ox-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Compiles Org Mode files to Hugo markdown files, so essentially duplicates a lot of the functionality of Hugo itself, but has the advantage that you don&amp;rsquo;t need any Hugo-specific syntax in your Org files to make them work.
To setup, add
dotspacemacs-configuration-layers &amp;#39;( ;; ... (org :variables org-enable-hugo-support t) ;; ... ) to spacemacs config. Sources: this Github comment, Shane Sveller.
Then if you put the following in your file:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hugo-orgmode</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-orgmode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-orgmode/</guid>
      <description>Writing Hugo in Org   Hugo is a site generator. Among other things it has native support for generating websites from collections of Emacs Org Mode files.
  What about a link to Emacs
  It&amp;rsquo;s as simple as putting .org files in the content/ directory of the the generated site. Hugo has built-in Org Mode support.
 Hugo will create one page per file. It supports a bunch of different file types out of the box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emacs cheat sheet</title>
      <link>/posts/emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/emacs/</guid>
      <description>Rename current file: SPC f R (from Spacemacs config) Open config file: SPC f e f (from Spacemacs config probably) Open buffer list: SPC b b Fuzzy file find: SPC p f Reload config (actually restart Emacs but preserve layout): SPC q r Find out what a key is bound to: C-h c &amp;lt;key&amp;gt; Still have not got tables to be able to align properly.  Trying multiple different versions, none work Tried multiple fonts (Fira Mono + Source Code Pro), since there was a suggestion that fonts that aren&amp;rsquo;t properly monospace would cause issues, but this also doesn&amp;rsquo;t fix anything.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>